<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tushar &amp; Yue</title>
    <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tushar &amp; Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Horrifying Near Death Experience</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/31-my-horrifying-near-death-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/31-my-horrifying-near-death-experience/</guid>
      <description>“I did something super awesome!” - Tushar
“Oh really? Oh let me guess… you managed to overcome your fear of bugs and now you are no longer scared of bugs. Is that correct big man?” - Diary
“OMG STOP JUDGING ME! THE BUG LOOKED REALLY FREAKING SCARY!!!!!” - Tushar *cries internally*
But really, the last few days have been pretty awesome for me because I got to go on a vacation with Yue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOOOOOOOOOPE! Pt. 2</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/30-nooooooooope-pt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/30-nooooooooope-pt-2/</guid>
      <description>Golden showers. Water sports. Natural LaCroix. Hint of hint of tea. Pee-wee Herman. Tinkle Tailor Soldier Spy. Beyonce’s hit single. Bladder sweat. Squirtle. Squeeze the lemon. H2Ohhhhh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOOOOOOOOOPE!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/29-nooooooooope/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/29-nooooooooope/</guid>
      <description>Aunt Flow. Time of month. Shark week. Strawberry week. On the rag. Crimson tide. Mother Nature. Code red. Bloody Mary. Lady business. The Red wedding. Carrie. Girl flu. Monthly friend. Natural cranberry juice. The curse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Goin Gorillas</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/28-we-goin-gorillas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/28-we-goin-gorillas/</guid>
      <description>Today we went to my favorite restaurant in Houston so far (well it’s technically a cafe inside a temple, but whatever…. I set a personal goal to not go this place until December so I would give myself 1 full year of extreme (you&amp;rsquo;re welcome Yue) diet and exercise before I would even consider eating like a horse again.
Well I didn’t reach that goal. I am not sad at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthday Celebrate You Must!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/27-birthday-celebrate-you-must/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/27-birthday-celebrate-you-must/</guid>
      <description>It was Yoda’s birthday today. We kind of missed it… but don’t tell him that… otherwise he might get mad and make lots of noise at night time and not let us sleep.
Anyways, I am glad he is part of Yue’s and my life. He is a little shithead, but he is my little shithead.
Live long and prosper!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Fancy Now</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/26-i-am-fancy-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/26-i-am-fancy-now/</guid>
      <description>Today I went my first official fancy ballet dressed super fancy (with whatever clothes I have in my closet). The ballet was performed in a gorgeous building with giant sculptures inside of it. The whole ceiling was shiny and our seats were REALLY high to the point that I was legitimately afraid I was going to fall. Thank God for Yue - she told me to don’t be a pussy, and be a man (I may or may not have made that part up).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking of You</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/25-thinking-of-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/25-thinking-of-you/</guid>
      <description>Yue and I spent this weekend celebrating Valentine’s Day. I cooked up some pasta and some dessert that I was pretty proud of. The best part of the whole night was when Yue presented me with a very moving note on the back of a photo collage she made. I wasn’t surprised at all. That’s why I love her.
I want to say, I am VERY happy when I am with Yue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year&#39;s Resolutions Suck!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/24-new-years-resolutions-suck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/24-new-years-resolutions-suck/</guid>
      <description>UGH… I am deciding to be healthy and go to gym and wake up at 5AM and have a breakfast and yada yada yada… Let’s see how long I can keep this up. I signed up for a gym membership at LA Fitness, took Yue there a few times now, and I think she enjoys it… mostly… She gets bored pretty easily. She sometimes offers me unhealthy food, that I am refusing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Year Surprise!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/23-a-new-year-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/23-a-new-year-surprise/</guid>
      <description>So Yue got back to Houston earlier than expected: on the NYE at 11pm. That meant we spent the NYE together… inside the apartment… eating some leftover food that I made. I was very happy to do that because I got to do it with Yue. TBH, I was very surprised when Yue told me that her flight was moved up and I excited the whole day! We shared a midnight kiss, and watched the 1st episode of This Is Us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Delightful Surprise!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/22-what-a-delightful-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/22-what-a-delightful-surprise/</guid>
      <description>Hi bud, how long has it been? Like 7 freaking months! Well, I have been a little busy, but mostly I just forgot about writing in you. Basically, Yue and I broke up for a while, but then we got back together. That’s a super short summary of what happened that you are privy to. The reason I am writing this very special entry here is because I am finally done with the website I am making for Yue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Moved in With Her</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/21-ive-moved-in-with-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/21-ive-moved-in-with-her/</guid>
      <description>I have been living with Yue for about a month now at her place. Our school vacation started on the 14th and since then we have been having a lot of fun! We went to Crystal Beach and took Yoda to the vet. We shopped around for a new phone at the Verizon store and Yue got a brand new phone!!! Unfortunately, I had a fight with my parents about Yue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Shithead</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/20-little-shithead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/20-little-shithead/</guid>
      <description>So today I found out that Yoda can sleep in bed with Yue… if he feels like it… Basically this little shithead annoys the crap out of me when we try to take a nap. He runs around and makes a lot of noise. Little shithead thinks it’s so much fun to play with the blinds when his parents are trying to sleep. I am sure he enjoys annoying us. We are the most important people in his life: we feed him, clean up after his shit and vomit, take him to the vet, give him medications, play with him, basically we serve his ass all day long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are Officially a Couple Now!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/19-we-are-officially-a-couple-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/19-we-are-officially-a-couple-now/</guid>
      <description>So we are officially a couple now. Why do you ask? Because we got in an argument about the silliest thing today. It was about overusing the diswasher for smallest number of dishes. My family does not use dishwashers. Yue, on the other hand, typically uses dishwasher pretty frequently. So we ended up fighting about how Yue was not able to handle any difficulties in life and would choose the more comforting option, even if it costs her money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are We a Couple?</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/18-are-we-a-couple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/18-are-we-a-couple/</guid>
      <description>I have been spending a lot of time at Yue’s place now. It’s almost like we are living together. I have to say, I really love living with her. I would not mind doing this for the rest of my life with her. The best part of this is that she told me today she felt like we were a couple. Awww 😀</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Love Burlington!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/17-i-love-burlington/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/17-i-love-burlington/</guid>
      <description>Today, Yue and I went shopping at Burlington coat factory and I loved it! I hope Yue loved it too, but we haven’t developed telepathic mind-melding communication yet. We ended up buying a lot of clothes. Yue helped me pick out some shirts and pants, and I gotta say, she has a good sense of fashion. I like shopping with her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Dun Messed Up Part Deux...</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/16-i-dun-messed-up-part-deux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/16-i-dun-messed-up-part-deux/</guid>
      <description>OK, so I made her cry again. What a fool! I honestly didn’t mean to, but it just happened. I was joking around too much this time. Rather than going into too many details, all I am going to say is that I need to be mindful of her limits. I feel pretty crummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Dun Messed Up...</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/15-i-dun-messed-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/15-i-dun-messed-up/</guid>
      <description>So this is awkward. Today, I made Yue cry. I didn’t mean to… it just… sort of happened. It happened because I was pressuring Yue to call her doctor’s office to get results of her tests back. I find that Yue is opposite of millenials - she never feels entitled to anything. I, on the other hand, want things done in a timely fashion, and I get a little flustered if other people aren’t doing their job right (yeah, I know, I would be a horrible boss).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh Happy Day!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/14-oh-happy-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/14-oh-happy-day/</guid>
      <description>Today we found out we passed our classes. I was really happy. Yue was really happy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giddy Up, Cowboy!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/13-giddy-up-cowboy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/13-giddy-up-cowboy/</guid>
      <description>Today, we went to see Rodeo with Pressida. It was a lot of fun; too loud and too extreme, just like the people watching it 😀. But the most important part of today was the fact that I cooked steak for her. I have been watching a lot of videos on youtube about how to cook steak, and today was the day I tried all of that out. We went to my place (yes, I cooked steak in my place…), and I cooked a rather below average and well done steak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Bum</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/12-beach-bum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/12-beach-bum/</guid>
      <description>Yue’s birthday celebration continues today. I am not going to lie, this is quite possibly the best weekend I have ever had. And it’s all made possible by Yue. We went to Galveston beach, parked my car illegally on the sand while worrying heavily about whether my tiny little Civic would be able to get out of the sand. It did… so that’s a good news! I love Honda. And btw, this was my very first visit to an actual beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Shawty, Its Your Birthday!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/11-go-shawty-its-your-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/11-go-shawty-its-your-birthday/</guid>
      <description>So today is Yue’s birthday. We have talked about what to do during this weekend for a while now. Our day today was filled with lots and lots of activities that I, alone, would never do all of them in one week. So that’s saying something. We went to the arboretum and hiked there and shared a tender moment. Well, a few tender moments. We went to the mall too! Walking at the Galleria with Yue is so much fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am No Sherlock</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/10-i-am-no-sherlock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/10-i-am-no-sherlock/</guid>
      <description>Lovely weather. Lovelier company all day from Yue. It was a very relaxing and focused study session, right after a bit of fun 😀. Yoda behaved nicely and I can tell Yue really appreciates me training him. Well she told me that directly, so I am no Sherlock. And oh, we passed CMD and that&amp;rsquo;s a cause for celebration. Term is almost over. Yue&amp;rsquo;s birthday is almost here. Never have I been looking forward to break than this term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definitely. Yes.</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/9-definitely-yes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/9-definitely-yes/</guid>
      <description>Oh boy. This day&amp;hellip; This day was pretty much the same as yesterday, with me freaking out, and Yue working her magic on me. Would I have survived PA school without her? Definitely yes. Would I also experience crippling anxiety, GERD, and PUD? Definitely yes. The good thing is that the hard tests are behind us, and yes, we are preparing for the possibility of remediating the anatomy course. Side note, she is a great patient to do a physical exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He&#39;s My Xanax</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/8-hes-my-xanax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/8-hes-my-xanax/</guid>
      <description>Oh boy. This day&amp;hellip; Ok, so Yue and I had a tiny bit of a freak out moment about the CMD tests. I was so distraught after taking my tests today, but after spending some time with Yue, all of my worries just melted away. She is my natural anxiolytic! Well, Yoda counts too. We are both considering the possibility of remediating. But together, we can make it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supreme B.E.A.S.T</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/7-supreme-beast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/7-supreme-beast/</guid>
      <description>Yue is a beast. She was in focus mode all weekend. I could definitely see the effort she is placing into studying. Such hard work better pay off! I was so proud of her today. In the zone, locked and loaded with no time for interruptions. That&amp;rsquo;s what I like to see. Proper prioritization. Plus, she looks cute when she is focused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Twas a Good Day!</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/6-twas-a-good-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/6-twas-a-good-day/</guid>
      <description>Today was a good day. Started out very stressful with waking up super early in the morning to cram for a test, but it ended with some nice relaxing time with Yue. With the pressure of the finals, I forgot how it felt like to take the time for some of the little things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Cares About Grades Anyways?</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/5-who-cares-about-grades-anyways/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/5-who-cares-about-grades-anyways/</guid>
      <description>Yue is seeing Professor Erdman about her grades for CMD. I&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize it was troubling her&amp;hellip; troubling her to the point of seeing Professor Erdman. I feel bad for not noticing this issue earlier! I felt like a shitty boyfriend. I should review materials with her. Oh and I was really proud of her for focusing on studying the whole day. No distractions. Almost like a student hopped up on caffeine cramming for the most important test of her life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Stop.</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/4-full-stop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/4-full-stop/</guid>
      <description>I felt like I can spend the rest of my life with this woman. No explanation needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is This Strange Feeling?</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/3-what-is-this-strange-feeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/3-what-is-this-strange-feeling/</guid>
      <description>Today I felt like I was loved. Genuinely loved by another human being. Yue has spent her very limited time in driving me around from campus to my apartment. And she is doing that with a sense of appreciation and I think only someone who truly loves me can have. Oh my, I am in trouble&amp;hellip; 😀</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s My Xanax</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/2-shes-my-xanax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/2-shes-my-xanax/</guid>
      <description>So I had a patient today in front of a few people. It didn’t really go well. I kept getting nervous and my flow was not good at all. I was quite disappointed and pretty upset, but Yue&amp;rsquo;s presence cured me of my afflictions. BTW that’s the most sophisticated sentence I will ever write. She is my natural anxiolytic. 😀</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So It Begins...</title>
      <link>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/1-so-it-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tusharandyue.github.io/posts/1-so-it-begins/</guid>
      <description>So this is my very first attempt at keeping a journal. I am pretty sure this is going to be a pretty rough journal. Not sure how long I can keep this going, but I am going to try to log something interesting about us in here. Plan is to make this into a website and surprise Yue. And I am no good with words, so Yue, this is an apology in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>